Guide to the ROADwomen Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Events and Programs, id134667
  - Various Events and Programs, id134695
    - Democracy Fest, 2005; id135054 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Houston Chronicle “Dems Watching", 1998; id135055 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - “It’s Worth a Closer Look", 1998; id135056 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - One Vote!, 1998; id135057 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Platform Wars, 1998; id135058 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Politics in the Park, 1998; id135059 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Poll Watcher, 2002; id135060 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Poll Watcher, undated; id135061 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Precinct 133 Primary, 2004; id135062 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - President Clinton, 1998; id135063 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - President’s Dinner, 2002; id135064 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Pride Parade, 2001; id135065 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Program Planning, 1997-1999; id135066 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Proposition 2, 2001; id135067 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Right to Vote, 2003; id135068 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Social Security, undated; id135069 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Organizations, id134668
  This series consists of flyers, brochures, and general information about the corresponding organization. The folders regarding the Harris County Democratic Party contain more information, such as correspondence between members of ROADwomen and the HCDP, as the two organizations worked closely together.
  - 21st Century Democrats, undated; id135072 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - ATLA’s List, 2002; id135073 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Ballots, 2001-2002; id135074 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Bar Association Polls, 2002; id135075 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Braeswood democrats, 2006; id135076 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Clinton Presidential Library, undated; id135077 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - D.R.A.W. Academy, 2002; id135078 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Emily’s List, 2002; id135079 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Gold PAC, undated; id135080 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Harris County Democratic Party, 2002, 2005; id135081 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Harris County Democratic Party, 2002; id135082 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Harris County Democratic Party, 2002-2003; id135083 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Harris County Democratic Party Chair Campaign, 2003; id135084 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Harris County Democratic Party, 2005; id135085 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Holocaust Museum-Houston, 2000; id135086 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Houston Area Women’s Center, 2002; id135087 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Houston Conservation Voters, 2001; id135088 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Houston Gay and Lesbian Political Caucus, 2002; id135089 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Houston Justice for Janitors, undated; id135090 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Houston Property Rights Association, 2002; id135091 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Human Rights Campaign, undated; id135092 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Jane’s Due Process, 2002; id135093 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Leadership 20/20, undated; id135094 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - League of Women Voters of Houston, 2002; id135095 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Legislative Study Group, 2002; id135096 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - NARAL/TARAL, 2002; id135097 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - National Democratic Party, 2002-2003; id135098 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - New Texas PAC, 2002; id135099 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - People for the American Way, 2005; id135100 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Planned Parenthood, 2001-2002; id135101 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Progressive Voters in Action, 2001-2002; id135102 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Republican National Committee, 2002; id135103 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - River Oaks Double Ds, 1996, 1998; id135104 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Texans Against Insurance Abuse, undated; id135105 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Texas Conference for Women, 2001; id135106 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Texas Democratic Party, 2000-2002; id135107 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Texas Democratic Party County Chairs, 2004; id135108 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Texas Democratic Women-Austin, 1997; id135109 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Texas Freedom Network, 2002; id135110 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Texas Human Rights Fund, 2001; id135111 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Texas Partnership, undated; id135112 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Texas Young Democrats, 2002; id135113 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Victory Fund, 2002; id135114 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Washington Spectator, September 2002; id135115 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - West U. Journal, October 1998; id135116 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Campaign Materials, id134669
  This series contains campaign materials for both Republican and Democrat candidates. The materials include flyers, stickers and other items pertaining to the candidates’ campaigns. Local Houston area, Texas state and national races are represented within the series. The voters guides are items released by different organizations and not specifically by ROADwomen.
  - Candidates, id134699
    - Greg Abbott, 1994; id135118 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Marty Akins, 2001-2002; id135119 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Elsa Alcala, 2002; id135120 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Russell Austin, 2001-2002; id135121 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Eric Andell, 2000; id135122 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Brooks Ballard, 2002; id135123 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Chris Bell, 2001-2002; id135124 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Ken Bentsen, 2001-2002; id135125 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - David Bernsen, 2001-2002; id135126 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Gary Block, 2002; id135127 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Sherry Boyles, 2002; id135128 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Jeff Brown, 2002; id135129 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Lee Brown, 2001-2002; id135130 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Peter Brown, undated; id135131 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Andrew C. Burks, 2001; id135132 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - R. Jack Cagle, 2001-2002; id135133 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Doug Cannon, undated; id135134 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Jean Carnahan, undated; id135135 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - John Caycee, 2002; id135136 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Lydia Clay-Jackson, undated; id135137 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Ellen Cohen, 2005; id135138 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Paul Colbert, 2002; id135139 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Mark Cole, 2001; id135140 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Bill Connolly, 2002; id135141 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - John Cornyn, 2001; id135142 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Cynthia Crowe, undated; id135143 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Debra Danburg, 2002; id135144 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Tom Daschle, undated; id135145 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Sheri Y. Dean, 2002; id135146 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Ernest DeLeon, undated; id135147 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Georgia Dempster, 2001-2002; id135148 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Donna Detamore, 2001; id135149 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Grant Dorfman, 2002; id135150 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Jim Downes, 2002; id135151 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Ada Edwards, 2001; id135152 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Chet Edwards, 2002; id135153 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Rodney Ellis, 2002; id135154 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Jennifer Elrod, 2002; id135155 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Diane Feiler, 2002; id135156 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Jimmie Lou Fisher, 2002; id135157 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Wanda McKee Fowler, 1994; id135158 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Kim Thompson Frost, 2001-2002; id135159 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Annette Galik, 2002; id135160 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Brent Gamble, 2002; id135161 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Roland Garcia, 2001; id135162 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Sylvia Garcia, 2002; id135163 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Mary Kay Green, 2002; id135164 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Grant U. Hardeway, Sr., 2002; id135165 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Ronnie Ellen Harrison, undated; id135166 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Laura Higley, 2001; id135167 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Andrea Hinckson, 2002; id135168 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Robert Hinojosa, 2002; id135169 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Charles Hixon, 2002; id135170 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Scott Hochberg, 2002; id135171 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Wallace Jefferson, 2002; id135172 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Dianne Johnson, undated; id135173 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Tim Johnson, undated; id135174 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Evelyn Keyes, 2002; id135175 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Stephen King, 2002; id135176 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Ron Kirk, 2002; id135177 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Donna Kohlhausen, undated; id135178 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Nick Lampson, 1996, 2002; id135179 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Mary Landrieu, 2001-2002; id135180 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Shelia Jackson Lee, 2002; id135181 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Margaret Mirabel, 2001-2003; id135182 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Rick Molina, 2002; id135183 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Dan Morales, 2001; id135184 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Bruce Mossier, 2002; id135185 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Linda Motheral, 2001; id135186 (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - Diana Musslewhite, 2002; id135187 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Sam Nuchia, 2001; id135188 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Austin O’Toole, 2002; id135189 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Annise Parker, 2001-2002; id135190 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Folder not used, id135191 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Jim Parsons, undated; id135192 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - David Patronella, 2001-2002; id135193 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Rick Perry, 2002; id135194 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - John F. Phillips, 2002; id135195 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Chellie Pingree, 2002; id135196 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Gordon Quan, 2001-2002; id135197 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Barbara Ann Randofsky, 2005; id135198 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Teresa Ramirez, 2002; id135199 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Tom Ramsay, 2002; id135200 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Tom Reed, 2002; id135201 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Tom Reiser, undated; id135202 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Tim Riley, 2002; id135203 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Herb Ritchie, 2002; id135204 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Carroll G. Robinson, 2001; id135205 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Pat Rosenberg, 2001; id135206 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Rob Rowland, 2002; id135207 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Tony Sanchez, 2001-2002; id135208 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Bennie Sanders, 2002; id135209 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Mike Schneider, 2001; id135210 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Mike Stafford, 2002; id135211 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Dalia Stokes, 2002; id135212 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Frank Svetlik, undated; id135213 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Senfronia Thompson, 2002; id135215 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Robert G. Torricelli, 2002; id135216 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Gabriel Vasquez, 2001; id135217 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Kirk Watson, 2002; id135218 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Lois Combs Weinberg, 2002; id135219 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Paul D. Wellstone, 2002; id135220 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Marc Whitehead, 2001-2003; id135221 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - John Whitmire, 2001-2002; id135222 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Julius Whittier, undated; id135223 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Claudia Williamson, 2001; id135224 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Ken Wise, 2002-2003; id135225 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Martha Wong, 2002; id135226 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Mike Wood, 2001-2002; id135227 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - John T. Woolridge, 2001; id135228 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Jeff Work, 2001; id135229 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Ken Yarbrough, 2002; id135230 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Jim York, 2002-2003; id135231 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Voter Guides, id134700
    - AARP, 2002; id135233 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Candidates Guide, 1998; id135234 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Candidates, undated; id135235 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Voter Guide, October 2003; id135236 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Election Materials, id134701
    - Election Clippings, 1998; id135238 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Election, 2000; id135239 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Republican/Democrat Platform, 1998; id135240 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Various Materials, id134670
  This series consists of materials that do not fit into any other series. The materials included are business cards, a VHS tape, a print out of the Declaration of Independence, as well as various newspaper and magazine clippings regarding varied issues.
  - Contacts/Electeds, 2004; id135242 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Declaration of Independence, 1998; id135243 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Notes, undated; id135244 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Phone Numbers and Business Cards, undated; id135245 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Various Materials, 1997-1998; id135246 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Various Materials, 2001-2002; id135247 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Various Materials, 2004; id135248 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - VHS Cassette “Hate Crimes", 2000; id135249 (Box 3, Folder 32)